A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Office of the President, Senior Advisor, Office Files of Frank DeGiovanni FA1876
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Subject files, 1990-2016; 2; 26.91 Cubic Feet 67.5 document boxes: 53.5 letter boxes and 14 legal boxes
  - Fannie Mae Self-Help Summit December 2009, Washington D.C. (Box 12, Folder 184)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit Fiscal Year 2010 - Programming, presentations, and correspondence, 2009-2011 (Box 12, Folder 185-187)
  - Meetings and correspondence with Pablo Farias and Barry Gaberman, 2002-2006 (Box 13, Folder 188)
  - Meeting with Pablo Farias, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 189)
  - Agit Kanitkar Program Officer Memo - Program Officer for Development Finance and Economic Security, New Delhi, India Office, 2007-2008 (Box 13, Folder 190)
  - Expanding Livelihood Opportunities for Poor Households Initiative (ELOPHI) October 2010 Learning Group Meeting (Box 13, Folder 191)
  - Ford Foundation 2010 Worldwide Meeting (Box 13, Folder 192)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit Fiscal Year 2010 - Programming (Box 13, Folder 193)
  - CredAbility Network, 2010 (Box 13, Folder 194)
  - Program Related Investments (PRI) process automation, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 195)
  - Ford Foundation February-March 2007 Program Leadership Meeting (Box 13, Folder 196)
  - African Safari Lodge (ASL) Program Related Investments (PRI) proposal, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 197)
  - ShoreCap Exchange study, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 198)
  - Ford Foundation assets programming review - Noteworthy accomplishments, 2004-2006 (Box 13, Folder 199)
  - 2007 Assets Quarterly Meeting (Box 14, Folder 200)
  - Ford Foundation assets rural programming, 2006-2007 (Box 14, Folder 201)
  - Rural economic development, 2004-2005 (Box 14, Folder 202)
  - Vietnam Chamber of Commerce and Industry (VCCI) Challenge Fund - William Smith, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 203)
  - PolicyLink equity growth model, 2011 (Box 14, Folder 204)
  - University of North Carolina Center for Community Capitalism (CCC) - Community Advantage Program (CAP) data analysis, 2006-2007 (Box 14, Folder 205)
  - Consultative Group to Assist the Poor (CGAP) Phase IV, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 206)
  - Center for Social Development - Savings plans, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 207)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit Fiscal Year 2011 Budget, 2010-2011 (Box 14, Folder 208)
  - Program Related Investments (PRI) Fiscal Year 2008 Monitoring, 2007-2008 (Box 14, Folder 209)
  - Graduation Pilots, 2006-2007 (Box 14, Folder 210)
  - Strengthening Southern Infrastructure progress report, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 211)
  - Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS) Economic Development unit Fiscal Year 2007 accomplishments (Box 14, Folder 212)
  - Rural Livelihoods Learning Group, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 213)
  - Program Related Investments (PRI) June 2007 Mid-Year Loss Reserve Meeting, 2006-2007 (Box 14, Folder 214)
  - Program Related Investments (PRI) September 2009 Year End Loss Reserve Meeting (Box 14, Folder 215)
  - Overhead Guidelines - Grants, 2007-2009 (Box 15, Folder 216)
  - National Community Stabilization Trust (NCST) Program Related Investment (PRI), 2009 (Box 15, Folder 217)
  - Fiscal Year 2009 Program Related Investments (PRIs), 2008-2009 (Box 15, Folder 218)
  - Program Related Investments (PRI) September 2010 Year End Loss Reserve Meeting (Box 15, Folder 219)
  - Program Related Investments (PRI) September 2011 Year End Loss Reserve Meeting (Box 15, Folder 220)
  - Indian Grameen Services (IGS), 2007-2008 (Box 15, Folder 221)
  - Line of Work Statements Team, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 222)
  - Financial Services for Poverty Reduction Line of Work Statements, 2008-2010 (Box 15, Folder 223)
  - Aspen Institute Business and Society Program (BSP), 2005-2006 (Box 15, Folder 224)
  - Brookings Institution - Hamilton Project, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 225)
  - Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS) Economic Development unit program strategy and change, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 226)
  - University of Michigan National Poverty Center (NPC), 2003-2005 (Box 15, Folder 227)
  - Coastal Enterprises and Shorebank Enterprise Pacific (SEP) grant, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 228)
  - Corporation for Enterprise Development (CFED) Board September 2005 Meeting (Box 15, Folder 229)
    The Corporation for Enterprise Development (CFED) is now called Prosperity Now.
  - Research Triangle Institute (RTI) - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship, and Downpayment (SEED) evaluation, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 230)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit Fiscal Year 2010 Line of Work budgets, 2008-2010 (Box 16, Folder 231)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Fiscal Year 2011 Foundation Administered Projects (FAP), 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 232)
  - Innovation Network, 2010 (Box 16, Folder 233)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit briefing to Luis Ubinas, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 234)
  - 2007 Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship, and Downpayment (SEED) grants (Box 16, Folder 235)
  - Assets programming - Miscellaneous proposals, correspondence, and notes, 2008-2011 (Box 16, Folder 236)
  - Rural poverty - Carsey Institute, University of New Hampshire, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 237)
  - BRAC Stichting, 2011 (Box 16, Folder 238)
  - Social Performance Task Force (SPTF) April 2006 Meeting, Rome, Italy (Box 16, Folder 239)
  - Center for Financial Services Innovation (CFSI), 2005-2006 (Box 16, Folder 240)
  - Aspen Institute Initiative on Financial Security (IFS), 2005-2006 (Box 16, Folder 241)
  - University of North Carolina Center for Community Capitalism (CCC) - Community Advantage Program (CAP) grants, 2004-2006 (Box 16, Folder 242)
  - MetroEdge, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 243)
  - Michael Barr, Regents of the University of Michigan, undated (Box 16, Folder 244)
  - Consultative Group to Assist the Poor (CGAP) Technology Initiative proposal, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 245)
  - Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS) Economic Development unit Fiscal Year 2008 programming (Box 17, Folder 246-247)
  - Affinity Group on Development Finance (AGDF) budget, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 248)
  - Program Officer Meeting questions, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 249)
  - Program Related Investments (PRI) Data System Project, undated (Box 17, Folder 250)
  - Scale strategies for asset building, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 251)
  - John Colborn Reflection Memo - Community College Bridges to Opportunity Initiative (CCBOI), 2007 (Box 17, Folder 252)
  - Consultative Group to Assist the Poor (CGAP) June 2008 Annual Meeting, Hyderabad, India (Box 17, Folder 253)
  - Detroit and Michigan grantmaking, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 254)
  - SKS Foundation Ultra Poor Program, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 255)
  - William Smith Program Officer Memo, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 256)
  - Research - Poverty and food security, 1999-2011 (Box 17, Folder 257-258)
  - Indian Grameen Services (IGS) Program Related Investment (PRI), 2008 (Box 17, Folder 259)
  - Living Cities July 2008 Investment Committee Meeting (Box 17, Folder 260)
  - ShoreBank Enterprise Detroit (SED), 2008 (Box 17, Folder 261)
  - Assets programming Fiscal Year 2008 programming (Box 17, Folder 262)
  - Program Related Investments (PRI) September 2008 Year End Loss Reserve Meeting (Box 18, Folder 263)
  - Center for Financial Services Innovation (CFSI) budget, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 264)
  - Social Performance Task Force (SPTF) Fiscal Year 2009, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 265)
  - Bill and Melinda Gates Foundation, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 266)
  - Mark Willis, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 267)
  - Detroit Meeting with Kresge Foundation, July 2008, 2007-2008 (Box 18, Folder 268)
  - Center for Financial Services Innovation (CFSI) reports, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 269)
  - Graduating the Global Poor into Microfinance and Living Cities, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 270)
  - ShoreCap Exchange (SCE), 2008 (Box 18, Folder 271)
  - University of North Carolina Center for Community Capital (CCC) - Community Advantage Program (CAP) delinquency, race, and credit scores, 2007-2008 (Box 18, Folder 272)
  - Housing crisis presentations, 2007-2008 (Box 18, Folder 273)
  - Institute of Development Studies (IDS) - Social protection, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 274)
  - African Safari Lodge (ASL) Foundation proposal, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 275)
  - Social rating fund proposal, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 276)
  - Vice President's Initiative on Affirmative Action, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 277)
  - Fondo Esperanza (FE), 2008 (Box 18, Folder 278)
  - Living Cities Subprime Working Group, 2007-2008 (Box 18, Folder 279-280)
  - Social Performance Task Force (SPTF), 2008 (Box 19, Folder 281)
  - Living Cities Capital Formation Working Group April 2008 call (Box 19, Folder 282)
  - Brave New Foundation (BNF) - Ford Foundation Economic Security Online Broadcast, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 283)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit Fiscal Year 2013-2014 programming (Box 19, Folder 284)
  - Building Economic Security Over a Lifetime (BESOL) 2013 Monitoring Sections 6-8 (Box 19, Folder 285)
  - Social Performance Task Force (SPTF) Annual Meeting, June 2013, Panama (Box 19, Folder 286)
  - Peru 2013 trip (Box 19, Folder 287)
  - Consultative Group to Assist the Poor (CGAP)-Ford Foundation Graduation Program Global Learning Event, February 2014, Paris, France, 2013-2014 (Box 19, Folder 288)
  - Program Related Investments (PRI) review and redesign consults selection, 2014 (Box 19, Folder 289)
  - Progress out of Poverty Index (PPI), 2014 (Box 19, Folder 290)
  - Building Economic Security Over a Lifetime (BESOL) 2013 Monitoring Sections 2 and 5 (Box 19, Folder 291)
  - Peer review - Expanding Livelihood Opportunities for Poor Households Initiative (ELOPHI) and Building Economic Security Over a Lifetime (BESOL) programs in South Africa and Mozambique, 2014 (Box 19, Folder 292)
  - Building Economic Security Over a Lifetime (BESOL) 2013 Monitoring Sections 3-4 (Box 19, Folder 293)
  - Community development corporations case studies - Notes, undated (Box 19, Folder 294)
  - Assets programming - Miscellaneous presentations, proposals, and reports, 2007-2013 (Box 20, Folder 295-296)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit Foundation Administered Projects (FAP), 2012 (Box 20, Folder 297)
  - Consultative Group to Assist the Poor (CGAP)-Ford Foundation Graduation Program Technical Guides drafts, 2014 (Box 20, Folder 298)
  - Expanding Livelihood Opportunities for Poor Households Initiative (ELOPHI) Desktop Review proposals, 2014 (Box 20, Folder 299)
  - Sustainable Food Lab (SFL) 2013 Paraguay and Brazil Learning Journey - Learning About Sugar (Box 20, Folder 300)
  - 12th Annual Citi Conference in Leadership and Ethics - New York University panel, 2015 (Box 20, Folder 301)
    Restricted – Open in 2026
  - Peru and Amsterdam, Netherlands 2013 trips receipts (Box 20, Folder 302)
  - May 2013 Amsterdam, Netherlands trip, 2005-2013 (Box 20, Folder 303)
  - Susan Kaaria December 2012 Handover Memo, 2012-2013 (Box 20, Folder 304)
  - 2013 Ethiopia trip - Consultative Group to Assist the Poor (CGAP)-Ford Foundation Graduation Pilot, 2011-2013 (Box 20, Folder 305)
  - Things to work on - Surveys and reports, 2013 (Box 20, Folder 306)
  - Sustainable Food Lab (SFL) meetings, 2013 (Box 20, Folder 307)
  - Xavier Briggs meetings - Strategy discussions, 2014 (Box 20, Folder 308)
  - Xavier Briggs meetings - Improving Access to Financial Services (Financial Justice), 2014 (Box 21, Folder 309)
  - Xavier Briggs meetings - Building Economic Security Over a Lifetime (BESOL), undated (Box 21, Folder 310)
  - Xavier Briggs meetings - Expanding Livelihood Opportunities for Poor Households Initiative (ELOPHI), 2012-2014 (Box 21, Folder 311)
  - Program Related Investments (PRI) Innovation Initiative consultant proposals, 2013-2014 (Box 21, Folder 312)
  - Xavier Briggs February 2014 Biweekly Meeting (Box 21, Folder 313)
  - Program Related Investments (PRI) meeting, 2013-2014 (Box 21, Folder 314)
  - Darren Walker July 2013 Biweekly Meeting (Box 21, Folder 315)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit program strategy, part 1, 2012-2014 (Box 21, Folder 316-319)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit program strategy, part 2, 2012-2013 (Box 22, Folder 320)
  - University of North Carolina Center for Community Capital (CCC) - Community Advantage Program (CAP) Self-Help, 2011-2015 (Box 22, Folder 321)
  - Ford Foundation Program Officers April 2015 Meeting - Community Advantage Program (CAP) Market for Low Income Homeownership (Box 22, Folder 322)
  - Homeownership and household wealth, 2013-2015 (Box 22, Folder 323)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit - Miscellaneous grants, Program Related Investments (PRI), and initiatives, 2013-2014 (Box 22, Folder 324)
  - Building Economic Security Over a Lifetime (BESOL) and Financial Products and Services (FPS)/Financial Justice meetings, 2013-2014 (Box 22, Folder 325)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit - Miscellaneous reports and presentations, 2013-2014 (Box 22, Folder 326)
  - Alternative Credit Technologies (ACT), 2009 (Box 22, Folder 327)
  - SaveNYC, 2008-2009 (Box 22, Folder 328)
  - University of North Carolina Center for Community Capital (CCC) - Community Advantage Program (CAP) data collection, 2008-2009 (Box 22, Folder 329)
  - Assets programming Fiscal Year 2009 - Proposals, presentations, and meetings, 2008-2009 (Box 23, Folder 330-331)
  - Program Related Investments (PRI) April 2009 Loss Reserve Meeting, 2008-2009 (Box 23, Folder 332)
  - Assets programming - Strategy, proposals, reports, and community development, part 1, 2005-2011 (Box 23, Folder 333-335)
  - Assets programming - Strategy, proposals, reports, and community development, part 2, 1992-2008 (Box 24, Folder 336)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) October 2010 Biennial Program Meeting (Box 24, Folder 337)
  - Ghana Microfinance Graduation Pilot - Targeting the Ultra Poor (TUP), 2010 (Box 24, Folder 338)
  - Expanding Livelihood Opportunities for Poor Households Initiative (ELOPHI) - Notes for Analysis of Patterns of Grant Making, 2010 (Box 24, Folder 339)
  - Global Colloquium on Savings and Conditional Cash Transfer programs, 2008-2010 (Box 24, Folder 340)
  - Line of Work Statements and Center for Financial Services Innovation (CFSI) presentations, 2008-2009 (Box 24, Folder 341)
  - Expanding Livelihood Opportunities for Poor Households Initiative (ELOPHI) October 2010 Second Learning Group Meeting (Box 24, Folder 342)
  - Affinity Group on Development Finance (AGDF) November 2008 Annual Meeting (Box 24, Folder 343)
  - Peru Graduation Pilot trip, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 344)
  - Living Cities Capital Formation Committee, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 345)
  - SaveNYC, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 346)
  - Social Performance Task Force (SPTF) November 2008 Social Investor Forum and Microfinance East January 2009 Annual Meeting, 2008-2009 (Box 24, Folder 347)
  - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship, and Downpayment (SEED) January 2009 Synthesis Report Meeting (Box 24, Folder 348)
  - Living Cities Catalyst Fund Meeting January 2009 Advisory Board Meeting (Box 24, Folder 349)
  - Peru Graduation Pilot, 2009 (Box 24, Folder 350)
  - Honduras Graduation Pilot, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 351)
  - Opportunity and Finance Network (OFN) - Community Development Financial Institutions (CDFI) Survey, 2009 (Box 24, Folder 352)
  - Assets programming transition, 2008-2009 (Box 24, Folder 353)
  - Innovations for Poverty Action (IPA) Targeting the Ultra Poor (TUP) 2009 Grant, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 354)
  - Americans for Financial Reform (AFR) memos, 2010 (Box 25, Folder 355)
  - Assets programming - Correspondence and meetings, 2007-2010 (Box 25, Folder 356-357)
  - Living Cities Integration Initiative July 2010 Subcommittee Selection Meeting (Box 25, Folder 358)
  - Reducing Poverty by Increasing Access to Financial Services Communications Strategy, undated (Box 25, Folder 359)
  - Financial crisis - Papers and reports, 2008-2009 (Box 25, Folder 360)
  - Microfinance Institutions User Reviews, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 361)
  - Ford Foundation Program Officer Meeting July 2009 Graduation Program Presentation, 2006-2009 (Box 25, Folder 362)
  - Miscellaneous materials - Targeting the Ultra Poor (TUP) and financial services, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 363)
  - United States Department of Housing and Urban Development Partnership for Transformation Fund, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 364)
  - Detroit - New Economy Initiative, undated (Box 25, Folder 365)
  - Ford Foundation Spring 2009 Line of Work Summaries (Box 25, Folder 366)
  - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship, and Downpayment (SEED) Advisory Board March 2006 Meeting (Box 25, Folder 367)
  - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship, and Downpayment (SEED) - University of Kansas, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 368)
  - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship, and Downpayment (SEED) correspondence and proposals, 2005-2006 (Box 26, Folder 369)
  - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship, and Downpayment (SEED) January 2006 Funder and Partner Meeting, 2005-2006 (Box 26, Folder 370)
  - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship, and Downpayment (SEED) Universal Model presentation, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 371)
  - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship, and Downpayment (SEED) - Center for Social Development (CSD) Proposal, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 372)
  - Ford Foundation Livelihood and Social Protection Program Convening, April 2014, Johannesburg, South Africa (Box 26, Folder 373)
  - Economic Policy Research Institute (EPRI) Savings and Investment Linkages (SAIL), 2012-2013 (Box 26, Folder 374)
  - World Food Programme (WFP) - Mozambique, 2014 (Box 26, Folder 375)
  - South Africa, 2014 (Box 26, Folder 376)
  - September 2013 Indonesia trip (Box 26, Folder 377)
    File contains a still image. The image is a small headshot photograph of Frank DeGiovanni.
  - October 2013 India trip (Box 26, Folder 378)
  - Aspen Institute July 2014 Financial Security Summit, 2013-2014 (Box 26, Folder 379)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit strategy - Memos and miscellaneous, 2008-2014 (Box 26, Folder 380)
  - Correspondence and proposals received on 2014 vacation, 2012-2014 (Box 27, Folder 381)
  - Financial assets program strategy - Reports and meetings, 2014-2015 (Box 27, Folder 382)
  - Financial assets program strategy - Reports and meetings, 2012-2015 (Box 27, Folder 383)
  - Graduation approach and financial products and services, 2013 (Box 27, Folder 384)
  - Rainforest Alliance and Ford Foundation New Delhi, India Office, 2013 (Box 27, Folder 385)
  - WealthWorks Cross Regional Convening, September 2013, Berea, Kentucky (Box 27, Folder 386)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit Foundation Administered Projects (FAP), 2011-2013 (Box 27, Folder 387)
  - Ford Foundation Office/Unit Description - Financial Assets unit, undated (Box 27, Folder 388)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit program strategy and grants, part 1, 2012-2014; File contains one still image (Box 27, Folder 389-390)
    File contains a photograph. The photograph is a small headshot photograph of Frank DeGiovanni.
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit program strategy and grants, part 2, 2014 (Box 28, Folder 391)
  - WealthWorks Second Cross Regional Convening, September 2013, Berea, Kentucky (Box 28, Folder 392)
  - Sustainable Food Lab (SFL) Mars Meeting, 2013 (Box 28, Folder 393)
  - 2013 Brazil trips (Box 28, Folder 394)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit programming - Reports and briefs, 2013 (Box 28, Folder 395)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit programming - Reports and meetings, part 1, 2013-2014 (Box 28, Folder 396-398)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit programming - Reports and meetings, part 2, 2013 (Box 29, Folder 399)
  - University of Kansas Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship, and Downpayment (SEED) research proposal, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 400)
  - New America Foundation (NAF) Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship, and Downpayment (SEED) proposal, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 401)
  - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship, and Downpayment (SEED) Oakland Livingston Human Services Association (OLHSA) implementation, 2005-2006 (Box 29, Folder 402)
  - Corporation for Enterprise Development (CFED) Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship, and Downpayment (SEED) renewal proposal, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 403-404)
  - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship, and Downpayment (SEED) request for proposals - Confederation for Enterprise Development (CFED) Universal Model, 2004-2005 (Box 29, Folder 405)
  - Meetings and Ford Foundation regional office visits - Briefing books and other materials, 2003-2015 (Box 30, Folder 406-408)
  - Ford Foundation Johannesburg, South Africa Regional Office - Economic development programming, 2007-2008 (Box 30, Folder 409)
  - Collective Action and Property Rights (CAPRi) Working Paper Nos. 81-90, 2008 (Box 30, Folder 410-411)
  - Ford Foundation Leadership Meeting - Theory of Change, 2011 (Box 30, Folder 412)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit Fiscal Year 2012-2013 Program Budget planning, 2010-2011 (Box 30, Folder 413)
  - Consultative Group to Assist the Poor (CGAP)-Ford Foundation Graduation 2015 Group Meeting, October 2011, Washington D.C. (Box 30, Folder 414)
  - Frank DeGiovanni notes and meeting materials, 2011-2012 (Box 30, Folder 415)
  - Fiscal Year 2012-2013 correspondence, 2011-2013 (Box 31, Folder 416)
  - Ford Foundation Human Rights Policy Protection, 2013 (Box 31, Folder 417)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit strategy, undated (Box 31, Folder 418)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit Theory of Change, 2014 (Box 31, Folder 419)
  - Better than Cash Alliance (BTCA) Technical Assistance Facility (TAF), 2014 (Box 31, Folder 420)
  - Committee on Sustainability Assessment (COSA), 2014 (Box 31, Folder 421)
  - Social Mobility, 2014 (Box 31, Folder 422)
  - Better than Cash Alliance (BTCA), 2014 (Box 31, Folder 423)
  - Measurement and Evaluation Working Group, 2012 (Box 31, Folder 424)
  - United Nations Research Institute for Social Development (UNRISD) Project Briefs, 2012 (Box 31, Folder 425)
  - Evaluator Roundtable, 2013 (Box 31, Folder 426)
  - Center for Financial Services Innovation (CFSI), 2002-2014 (Box 31, Folder 427)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit March 2011 Quarterly Review (Box 31, Folder 428)
  - Meetings with Pablo Farias, 2010-2011 (Box 31, Folder 429)
  - EBUG 2011 grant list (Box 31, Folder 430)
  - Grants and budget system 2011 release notes (Box 31, Folder 431)
  - Impact assessment terms, undated (Box 31, Folder 432)
  - Comparison of Program Officer to Senior Program Investment Manager job descriptions, undated (Box 31, Folder 433)
  - Living Cities Local Integration Initiative request for proposals, 2009 (Box 31, Folder 434)
  - Aspen Institute Business and Society Program proposal, 2009 (Box 31, Folder 435)
  - Social Performance Reporting Award, 2009 (Box 31, Folder 436)
  - Social Performance Task Force (SPTF) Steering Committee, 2009 (Box 31, Folder 437)
  - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship, and Downpayment (SEED) Advisory Board, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 438)
  - Corporation for Enterprise Development (CFED)/Federal Reserve System (FRS) Asset Building Initiative, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 439)